http://www.wavescape.co.za/wavescape-privacy-policy.html

Remember Me
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
SUBSCRIBE to LIVE STREAM
Melkbos (Live Stream)
Table View (Live Stream)
Tablemountain View
Big Bay
Three Anchor Bay
Clifton 4th (Live Stream)
Noordhoek Beach (Live Stream)
Long Beach (Live Stream)
Kalk Bay (Live Stream)
Muizenberg Corner
Muizenberg (Live Stream)
Strand (Live Stream)
Knysna Heads
Shelly Beach
Scottburgh (daily photos)
Durban (Live Stream)
Thu, 16 June 2016
Wavescape adheres to strict privacy policy guidelines as per accepted PII (Personally Identifiable Information) laws and best practises. Below, please find our privacy policy, which is a legally binding promise from us to you as a user of this website.
www.wavescape.co.za Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled for anyone concerned with how 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used on Wavescape. PII, as used in US privacy law and global information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM THE PEOPLE THAT VISIT OUR WEBSITE?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience and to receive subscription services.WHEN DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order for our cam subscription, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site.
Provide us with feedback on our products or services
HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To improve our website in order to better serve you.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
HOW DO WE PROTECT VISITOR INFORMATION?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks. All sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We have implemented security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions and credit card numbers are processed through a third party secured gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
DO WE USE 'COOKIES'?
We as Wavescape do not use cookies for tracking purposes. However, for example, as a third party vendor, Google uses cookies on our site to serve ads based on user preferences.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
However, you can still place orders.
THIRD-PARTY DISCLOSURE - NB
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.THIRD-PARTY LINKS
We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.
GOOGLE
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
• Remarketing with Google AdSense • Google Display Network Impression Reporting • Demographics and Interests Reporting
We - along with third-party vendors such as Google - use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
OPTING OUT
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
ACCORDING TO CALOPPA WE AGREE TO THE FOLLOWING:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on this Privacy Policy Page
Users are able to change their personal information by logging in to their account
HOW DOES OUR SITE HANDLE DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
DOES OUR SITE ALLOW THIRD-PARTY BEHAVIORAL TRACKING?
It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (CHILDREN ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
FAIR INFORMATION PRACTICES
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users via email within 1 business day
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM ACT
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. • Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
• NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses. • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way. • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters. • Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used. • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly. • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails
• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contact Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.www.wavescape.co.zapaul@wavescape.co.za
< Prev
Next >
Joomla SEF URLs by Artio
JavaScript must be enabled in order for you to use the Nurte Facebook Like Box. However, it seems JavaScript is either disabled or not supported by your browser. To use the Nurte Facebook Like Box, enable JavaScript by changing your browser options, then try again.
Twitter
Fri Oct 09 07:39:31 +0000 2020
KZN South Coast -- Cool weather ahead as a bit of winter rules the rooster, with Friday light going moderate crispy… https://t.co/1xcSQpvbk2
Fri Oct 09 07:26:18 +0000 2020
@KapteinKai Your wish is our command @KapteinKai - looks like proper rain today and tomorrow!
Fri Oct 09 07:25:24 +0000 2020
We're in a weird limbo between winter and summer, with heavy rains along the southern cape today, chilly SE winds a… https://t.co/VRbP0r6Afo
Thu Oct 08 13:21:09 +0000 2020
Three hurricanes to bust the record of 28 hurricanes in the 2005 season, and scarily, Delta ( #25) comes a full mont… https://t.co/Afir636JDM
Follow Wavescape on Twitter
Privacy PolicyAbout UsSitemapAdvertiser EnquiriesSmall Print
Wavescape Mk IV - Developed by Kalemanzi Media Solutions
